<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>10 &#43; 10 Years</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on 10 &#43; 10 Years</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.139.2</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Finale</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/finale/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/finale/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;tipping-point&#34;&gt;Tipping Point&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After enduring enough abuse in my own home from the treacherous suitors, the time had come to leave my mark and take back what’s rightfully mine. With the help of Athena we planned an archery contest through my wife Penelope, where the winner gets to take her hand in marriage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Of course no suitors could match my raw strength, so it is all a ploy to finally rid of all the parasites in my home and from my family. They’ve exhausted all of my resources and made a fool of my home, so it is only right I deplete them of their pathetic lives. I was told by fate that this day would come, and what a blessing it is to execute this final act beside my son—his first real test.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reunion</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/reunion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/reunion/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;telemachus&#34;&gt;Telemachus&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I made it. By the will of the Gods and the hand of fate, I have landed in rocky Ithaca, the home I’ve been absent from for two long decades. My family has grown without me, and now it was time to unite this family and my city.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I made it to my old swineherd and friend Eumaeus’ place but dressed as an old wrinkly beggar not to blow my cover. We had friendly chats, and then came my great son Telemachus! I have not seen my boy since he was a little baby. He is so big and muscular now after his father, but I had to hold back the strongest urges to hug my own son because of my disguise.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Family</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/family/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/family/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;voyage&#34;&gt;Voyage&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After turning my men into pigs, the sorceress Circe tasked me with a journey no man has done before: to travel to the house of Hades by ship. She told me I must seek the blind prophet Tiresias for his advice on my homecoming. I wept, knowing that this task would not be possible, but Circe affirmed my resourcefulness and advised me to let the wind blow me to the shores of the Underworld. And so I did.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loss</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/loss/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/loss/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-cyclopes&#34;&gt;The Cyclopes&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After dragging my men back from the tempting lotus plants, we could not afford another detour. We needed to get back home. We sailed the grayish waters until we arrived at the land of the Cyclopes, the men and women who put their trust in gods and have no laws. They lack a second eye and their physique is like that of the gods.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We spent the first night on the ship and when Dawn took the sky we set out to question their hospitality and fear of the gods. I brought my twelve most trustworthy men with me to a high cave occupied by one of these massive men. We waited until nightfall until the giant came home with a bundle of wood intended for fire. Huddled up in the corner, we waited until the Cyclops lit his fire and noticed our presence.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
